All right, big blue. Let's welcome Jack
Kelly, linebacker from BYU, your
sixth-round pick, 193rd pick overall.
Jack rocking the stash right now.
Absolutely love it, man. How's it feel,
bro, now that you're officially a New
York Giant? I mean, it's surreal, for
sure. I mean, it's something that I've
dreamt of since I was a kid.
Just grateful for this opportunity,
ready to get to work, and
grateful for everything. What were you
doing when you got the 201 call on your
cell phone? And then what was the
emotions like after you know Joe Shane
and John Harbaugh talked to you and told
you that this was the team that was
drafting you.
Yeah, so we were all actually out back,
just working on some chipping for golf,
and heard my phone ring, got up.
I mean, the emotions, I can't really
describe. I was just super happy,
grateful, kind of go through all the
moments that it took to get me here,
and now I'm just super grateful for the
opportunity, ready to get to work.
>> And you talk about it's been a long
journey to get here. You went to high
school in Salt Lake County. You go to
Weber State. You transfer to BYU. I
mean, you go on an absolute tear, go
beast mode, 10-plus sacks, double-digit
sacks last year. I mean, just talk about
that journey, man. Like, you know,
what's it what's it been like, the ups
and downs, the highs and lows, to
finally get to the goal, and that's the
NFL?
Yeah, I think it's really just about
putting in the work, especially when
people aren't looking. You might have a
bad game. You got to overcome that with
your mindset.
Just always believe in yourself. I mean,
I can't thank the coaches I've had in my
life enough for what they've done for me
starting football
a little later than most people start,
just being able to have those coaches to
teach me the right way to play, and
ultimately give me the opportunity to be
at this and have this opportunity.
What's a couple things you're looking
forward to most in or around the city?
Definitely the food. I'm definitely
looking forward to eating some good
food.
Just being around the guys, meeting
everyone. I think that's a big thing,
and playing ball. I think that's the
number one thing is just getting out
there and being with everyone, playing
ball, having fun. Real football guy,
man. Well, congratulations. Can't wait
to you get out here for for rookie camp
and OTAs, and we're lucky to have you on
board, man.
Yes, sir. I appreciate you so much.
>> [music]